Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series VII: Writing Materials
  - Sub-series A: Friends
    - Writing Materials – Friends, 1983-1986
      - Dinner with Japanese Ambassador Matsunaga, 1986 February-March (Box 332, Folder 9)
      - Freight Bills, 1986 March-April (Box 332, Folder 10)
      - Biography of Hadi Hochmuth, 1986 April (Box 332, Folder 11)
      - Tennessee Bookselling Community – Key People, 1986 (Box 332, Folder 12)
      - Comments on Friends for use on Dust Jacket, 1986 (Box 332, Folder 13)
      - Memphis International Festival, 1986 April-May (Box 332, Folder 14)
      - Book Review by John James, 1986 May (Box 332, Folder 15)
      - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 332, Folder 16)
      - Public Events, 1986 (Box 332, Folder 17)
      - TV Appearances, 1986 May (Box 332, Folder 18)
      - “A Bushel of Books for Tennessee’s Homecoming”, 1986 May 15-16 (Box 332, Folder 19)
      - Remarks of Jack Kemp in Tokyo, 1985 August 23 (Box 332, Folder 20)
      - Tennessee on Tour, 1986 May (Box 332, Folder 21)
      - Article in Tokyo Newspaper, 1986 June 18 (Box 332, Folder 22)
      - New York Times Article, 1986 July 15 (Box 332, Folder 23)
      - Tennessee/Japan Society Dinner, 1986 May 23 (Box 332, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence – Japanese Keidanren, 1984 (Box 332, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence – Takashi Ishihara, 1984 March-May (Box 332, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence – Robin Hood, 1984-1985 (Box 332, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence – Lisa Drew, 1984 (Box 332, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence – Letters Concerning Bridge to the Sun by Mrs. Terasaki, 1985 January 16 (Box 332, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence – Lorraine Abbott, 1985 July (Box 332, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence – Tadashi Akaishi, 1985 August (Box 332, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence – Tadashi Akaishi, 1985 September (Box 332, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence – Tadashi Akaishi, 1986 February (Box 332, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence – Ed Liden, 1985 March-April (Box 332, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence – Ed Liden, 1985 July (Box 332, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence – Mitsuya Goto, 1985 May (Box 332, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence – Maria Seigenthaler, 1985 August-September (Box 332, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence – Phillip Moffitt, 1985 December (Box 332, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence – Saburo Nobuki, 1986 February (Box 332, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence – William Morris Jr., 1985 November (Box 332, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence – Bill Brock, 1985 November (Box 332, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence – Harper & Row Sales Managers, 1986 February (Box 332, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence – Katz Takeda, 1986 February-April (Box 332, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence – Wilma Dykeman, 1985 March – 1986 May (Box 332, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence – Letters Regarding Friends Tour, 1986 February (Box 332, Folder 45)
      - Correspondence – Mike Mansfield, 1986 March-April (Box 332, Folder 46)
    - Writing Materials – Friends, 1986
      - Correspondence – Nicholas T. Smith, 1986 April (Box 333, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence – Lewis Lavine, 1986 March-May (Box 333, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence – M.H. Miki, 1986 April (Box 333, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence – Lists of Those to Receive Friends, 1986 (1 of 5) (Box 333, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence – Lists of Those to Receive Friends, 1986 (2 of 5) (Box 333, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence – Lists of Those to Receive Friends, 1986 (3 of 5) (Box 333, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence – Lists of Those to Receive Friends, 1986 (4 of 5) (Box 333, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence – Lists of Those to Receive Friends, 1986 (5 of 5) (Box 333, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence – Thank-you Letters for Copies of Friends, 1986 (1 of 4) (Box 333, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence – Thank-you Letters for Copies of Friends, 1986 (2 of 4) (Box 333, Folder 10)
    - Writing Materials – Friends, 1983-1986
      - Correspondence – Thank-you Letters for Copies of Friends, 1986 (3 of 4) (Box 334, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence – Thank-you Letters for Copies of Friends, 1986 (4 of 4) (Box 334, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence – Miscellaneous Letters, 1983-1984 (Box 334, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence – Sample Japan Book Letters, 1986 (Box 334, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence – Ann Harakawa, 1986 April (Box 334, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence – Mitsuya Goto, 1986 May 2 (Box 334, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence – Sam Williams, 1986 May 6 (Box 334, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence – Ward Archer, 1986 May 9 (Box 334, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence – Takashi Miyazaki, 1986 May-June (Box 334, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence – Lucien Ellington, 1986 May 21 (Box 334, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence – Shinichi Okamoto, 1986 June 11 (Box 334, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence – Memo to Honey and Carole, 1986 June 19 (Box 334, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence – Retirement of Saburo Nobuki and Tadashi Akaishi, 1986 July-September (Box 334, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence – Norishige Hasegawa, 1986 September 17 (Box 334, Folder 14)
      - Business Cards, undated (Box 334, Folder 15)
      - Drafts of Text, undated (Box 334, Folder 16)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 1, 1985 July 7 (Box 334, Folder 17)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 2, 1985 July 7 (Box 334, Folder 18)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 1, circa 1985 (1 of 4) (Box 334, Folder 19)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 1, circa 1985 (2 of 4) (Box 334, Folder 20)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 1, circa 1985 (3 of 4) (Box 334, Folder 21)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 1, circa 1985 (4 of 4) (Box 334, Folder 22)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 2, circa 1985 (1 of 4) (Box 334, Folder 23)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 2, circa 1985 (2 of 4) (Box 334, Folder 24)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 2, circa 1985 (3 of 4) (Box 334, Folder 25)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 2, circa 1985 (4 of 4) (Box 334, Folder 26)
    - Writing Materials – Friends, 1985-1986
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 3, circa 1985 (1 of 3) (Box 335, Folder 1)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 3, circa 1985 (2 of 3) (Box 335, Folder 2)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 3, circa 1985 (3 of 3) (Box 335, Folder 3)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 5, circa 1985 (1 of 3) (Box 335, Folder 4)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 5, circa 1985 (2 of 3) (Box 335, Folder 5)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 5, circa 1985 (3 of 3) (Box 335, Folder 6)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 6, circa 1985 (1 of 3) (Box 335, Folder 7)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 6, circa 1985 (2 of 3) (Box 335, Folder 8)
      - Book Drafts – Chapter 6, circa 1985 (3 of 3) (Box 335, Folder 9)
      - Excerpts from Friends in Japanese Magazines, 1986 (1 of 2) (Box 335, Folder 10)
      - Excerpts from Friends in Japanese Magazines, 1986 (2 of 2) (Box 335, Folder 11)
      - Japanese American Journey – The Story of a People, 1985 (Box 335, Folder 12)
  - Sub-series B: Six Months Off
    - Writing Materials – Six Months Off –, 1986-1989
      - Chapter Drafts Notebook, undated (Box 336, Folder 1)
      - Book Reviews and Articles, 1988-1989 (Box 336, Folder 2)
      - Administrative and Financial Material, 1988-1989 (Box 336, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous Notes and Materials, 1988-1989 (Box 336, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence – General, 1988-1989 (Box 336, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence – Reading File, 1988 September-October (Box 336, Folder 6)
      - Photocopy of Notebook – pg. 1-191, 1986 (Box 336, Folder 7)
      - Photocopy of Notebook – pg. 192-282, 1986 (Box 336, Folder 8)
    - Writing Materials – Six Months Off –, 1986-1987
      - Photocopy of Notebook – pg. 283-430, 1986-1987 (Box 337, Folder 1)
      - Photocopy of Notebook – pg. 431-594, 1987 (Box 337, Folder 2)
      - Photocopy of Notebook – pg. 595-740, 1987 (Box 337, Folder 3)
      - Photocopy of Notebook – pg. 741-859, 1987 (Box 337, Folder 4)
      - Photocopy of Notebook – pg. 860-951, 1987 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Writing Materials – Six Months Off –, 1988
      - Miscellaneous Corrections, 1988 (Box 338, Folder 1)
      - Draft with Corrections #1, 1988 (1 of 2) (Box 338, Folder 2)
      - Draft with Corrections #1, 1988 (2 of 2) (Box 338, Folder 3)
      - Draft with Corrections #2, 1988 (1 of 2) (Box 338, Folder 4)
      - Draft with Corrections #2, 1988 (2 of 2) (Box 338, Folder 5)
      - Draft with Corrections #3, 1988 (1 of 4) (Box 338, Folder 6)
    - Writing Materials – Six Months Off –, 1988
      - Draft with Corrections #3, 1988 (2 of 4) (Box 339, Folder 1)
      - Draft with Corrections #3, 1988 (3 of 4) (Box 339, Folder 2)
      - Draft with Corrections #3, 1988 (4 of 4) (Box 339, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 339, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence from Australia, 1987 (Box 339, Folder 5)
      - Morrow Publicity, 1988 (Box 339, Folder 6)
      - Maps, 1988 (Box 339, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 339, Folder 8)
  - Sub-series C: Governor Book
    - Writing Materials – Governor Book –, 1985-1987
      - Governor Book, 1985-1987 (Box 339, Folder 9)
  - Sub-series D: We Know What to Do
    - Writing Materials – We Know What to Do –, 1994
      - Summary Book –, circa 1994 (1 of 2) (Box 340, Folder 1)
      - Summary Book – circa 1994 (2 of 2) (Box 340, Folder 2)
      - Transcripts of Conversations, 1994 (1 of 7) (Box 340, Folder 3)
      - Transcripts of Conversations, 1994 (2 of 7) (Box 340, Folder 4)
      - Transcripts of Conversations, 1994 (3 of 7) (Box 340, Folder 5)
      - Transcripts of Conversations, 1994 (4 of 7) (Box 340, Folder 6)
      - Transcripts of Conversations, 1994 (5 of 7) (Box 340, Folder 7)
      - Transcripts of Conversations, 1994 (6 of 7) (Box 340, Folder 8)
    - Writing Materials – We Know What to Do –, 1994-1995
      - Transcripts of Conversations, 1994 (7 of 7) (Box 341, Folder 1)
      - Dictation from the Drive, 1994 (Box 341, Folder 2)
      - Master Copy – Inserts, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 3)
      - Master Copy – Prologue, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 4)
      - Master Copy – Table of Contents, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 5)
      - Master Copy – Chapter 1, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 6)
      - Master Copy – Chapter 2, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 7)
      - Master Copy – Chapter 3, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 8)
      - Master Copy – Chapter 4, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 9)
      - Master Copy – Chapter 5, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 10)
      - Master Copy – Chapter 6, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 11)
      - Master Copy – Chapter 7, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 12)
      - Master Copy – Chapter 8, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 13)
      - Master Copy – Chapter 9, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 14)
      - Master Copy – Chapter 10, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 15)
      - Master Copy – Chapter 11, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 16)
      - Master Copy – Acknowledgments, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 17)
      - Final Corrected Manuscript, 1995 (1 of 3) (Box 341, Folder 18)
      - Final Corrected Manuscript, 1995 (2 of 3) (Box 341, Folder 19)
      - Final Corrected Manuscript, 1995 (3 of 3) (Box 341, Folder 20)
    - Writing Materials – We Know What to Do, 1995
      - Complete Book Draft – Chapters 1-5, 1995 (Box 342, Folder 1)
      - Complete Book Draft – Chapters 6-13, 1995 (Box 342, Folder 2)
      - Complete Book Draft – Chapters 9-11, 1995 (Box 342, Folder 3)
      - Complete Book Draft – Side Trips and Chapter 10, 1995 (Box 342, Folder 4)
      - Draft with Notes, 1995 (1 of 2) (Box 342, Folder 5)
      - Draft with Notes, 1995 (2 of 2) (Box 342, Folder 6)
      - Copy Editor’s Corrected Proof, 1995 May (1 of 2) (Box 342, Folder 7)
      - Copy Editor’s Corrected Proof, 1995 May (2 of 2) (Box 342, Folder 8)
      - Epilogue, 1995 June (Box 342, Folder 9)
      - Lamar’s Epilogue, 1995 (Box 342, Folder 10)
      - Epilogue with Schwalbe Edits, 1995 (Box 342, Folder 11)
      - Checker Finn Epilogue, 1995 (Box 342, Folder 12)
    - Writing Materials – We Know What to Do –, 1983-1995
      - Henning Chapter – Rewrite, 1995 (Box 343, Folder 1)
      - Lamar’s Edited Foreword, 1995 (Box 343, Folder 2)
      - Foreword Final, 1995 (Box 343, Folder 3)
      - Mickey Hershkowitz Draft Version, 1995 (1 of 2) (Box 343, Folder 4)
      - Mickey Hershkowitz Draft Version, 1995 (2 of 2) (Box 343, Folder 5)
      - Flap Copy, 1995 (Box 343, Folder 6)
      - Bailey/Casse Edits, 1995 (1 of 2) (Box 343, Folder 7)
      - Bailey/Casse Edits, 1995 (2 of 2) (Box 343, Folder 8)
      - Gary Hart Information, 1983-1984 (Box 343, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1995 (Box 343, Folder 10)
      - Lamar’s Changes, 1995 (1 of 3) (Box 343, Folder 11)
      - Lamar’s Changes, 1995 (2 of 3) (Box 343, Folder 12)
      - Lamar’s Changes, 1995 (3 of 3) (Box 343, Folder 13)
      - Scott Hamilton’s Corrections, 1995 July (Box 343, Folder 14)
      - Biederman’s Changes, 1995 (Box 343, Folder 15)
      - Checker’s Corrections, 1995 (Box 343, Folder 16)
    - Writing Materials – We Know What to Do –, 1994-1995
      - Checker Finn’s Changes, 1995 (Box 344, Folder 1)
      - Book Promotion, 1995 August (Box 344, Folder 2)
      - Side Trips: Graceland, undated (Box 344, Folder 3)
      - Stories from the Drive Across America, undated (Box 344, Folder 4)
      - Personal Notes, 1994-1995 (Box 344, Folder 5)
      - Book Audio Tape, 1995 (Box 344, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence – Paul Weyrich, 1995 (Box 344, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series E: The Tennesseans
    - Writing Materials – The Tennesseans –, 1979-1986
      - Concept and Style of the Book, circa 1980 (Box 345, Folder 1)
      - Notes on the Book, circa 1980 (Box 345, Folder 2)
      - Proposed Project Schedule, circa 1980 (Box 345, Folder 3)
      - Arrangements with Robin Hood, 1979 (Box 345, Folder 4)
      - List of Places to Focus on in The Tennesseans, circa 1980 (Box 345, Folder 5)
      - Essay Sent to Barry Parker by Larry Stone, 1980 February 1 (Box 345, Folder 6)
      - Marketing Strategy, 1980 May (Box 345, Folder 7)
      - Contract for The Tennesseans, 1980 June 25 (Box 345, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1980 May-June (Box 345, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1980 August-October (Box 345, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 1980 September-1981 September (Box 345, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 345, Folder 12)
      - Chapter 1 Drafts – circa, 1980 (Box 345, Folder 13)
      - Book Promotion, 1981 September-October (Box 345, Folder 14)
      - Photograph Permissions, 1981 (Box 345, Folder 15)
      - Reception and Exhibit, 1981 September 24 (Box 345, Folder 16)
      - Requests for Autographed Copies, 1981 (Box 345, Folder 17)
      - Book Donations, 1981-1984 (Box 345, Folder 18)
      - Copies Sent Out, 1981-1986 (Box 345, Folder 19)
      - Royalties, 1980-1983 (Box 345, Folder 20)
      - Book Review, 1982 (Box 345, Folder 21)
      - Thank You Letters, 1981-1985 (Box 345, Folder 22)
- Series VIII: University of Tennessee President’s Papers
  - Sub-series A: Subject Files
    - UT President’s Papers – Subject Files, 1983-1990
      - Adult Education, 1986-1989 (Box 346, Folder 1)
      - Alcohol, 1988-1989 (Box 346, Folder 2)
      - Athletics/Academics, 1986-1989 (Box 346, Folder 3)
      - Career Ladder, 1983-1989 (Box 346, Folder 4)
      - Career Ladder, 1987-1990 (1 of 2) (Box 346, Folder 5)
      - Career Ladder, 1987-1990 (2 of 2) (Box 346, Folder 6)
      - Center for Strategic and International Studies, 1989 (Box 346, Folder 7)
      - Channel One, 1989-1990 (Box 346, Folder 8)
      - Classrooms of the Future, 1989-1990 (Box 346, Folder 9)
      - Clay County Grant Applications, 1988 (Box 346, Folder 10)
      - College Entrance Exams, 1989 (Box 346, Folder 11)
      - College: Is it for Everybody?, 1989-1990 (Box 346, Folder 12)
      - Community Colleges, 1989-1990 (Box 346, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence Courses, 1988-1989 (Box 346, Folder 14)
    - UT President’s Papers – Subject Files, 1983-1990
      - Dormitory Life – circa, 1989 (Box 347, Folder 1)
      - Education Summit, 1989 (Box 347, Folder 2)
      - Foreign Language, 1989-1990 (Box 347, Folder 3)
      - Freshmen Stress, 1987-1990 (Box 347, Folder 4)
      - Geography Education, 1988-1989 (Box 347, Folder 5)
      - Gifted Students, 1983-1989 (Box 347, Folder 6)
      - Holding Children Back, 1986-1989 (Box 347, Folder 7)
      - Homework, 1989 (Box 347, Folder 8)
      - How do we Know What Kids are Learning?, 1987-1990 (Box 347, Folder 9)
      - How Does a Town Fix Its Schools?, 1989-1990 (Box 347, Folder 10)
      - How to Improve Your Local School, 1984-1989 (Box 347, Folder 11)
      - Japanese Education, 1988-1990 (Box 347, Folder 12)
      - Keeping Kids in School, 1987-1990 (Box 347, Folder 13)
      - Learning Disabilities, 1983-1988 (Box 347, Folder 14)
      - Learning Forum SuperCamp, 1988 (Box 347, Folder 15)
      - Libraries, 1989-1990 (Box 347, Folder 16)
      - Memo Book – circa, 1990 (Box 347, Folder 17)
    - UT President’s Papers – Subject Files, 1981-1991
      - Math and Science, 1988-1990 (1 of 2) (Box 348, Folder 1)
      - Math and Science, 1988-1990 (2 of 2) (Box 348, Folder 2)
      - Math and Science Education, 1989 (Box 348, Folder 3)
      - Melissa Poe, 1989-1990 (Box 348, Folder 4)
      - National Education Goals, 1990 (Box 348, Folder 5)
      - New Ways to Beat Drugs, 1987-1990 (Box 348, Folder 6)
      - Next Century Schools, 1989 (Box 348, Folder 7)
      - Paying for College, 1989-1990 (Box 348, Folder 8)
      - Picking a College, circa 1989 (Box 348, Folder 9)
      - President Bush’s Education Policy, 1989-1990 (Box 348, Folder 10)
      - School Choice, 1988-1990 (Box 348, Folder 11)
      - School Choice – White House Workshop, 1989 January 10 (Box 348, Folder 12)
      - School Nutrition, 1981-1987 (Box 348, Folder 13)
      - School Preparation, 1989-1990 (Box 348, Folder 14)
      - Secretary of Education, 1991 (1 of 2) (Box 348, Folder 15)
      - Secretary of Education, 1991 (2 of 2) (Box 348, Folder 16)
    - UT President’s Papers – Subject Files, 1985-1990
      - Should Your Teenager Go Abroad?, 1988-1990 (Box 349, Folder 1)
      - Studying, 1989 (Box 349, Folder 2)
      - Taylor Plan, 1990 (Box 349, Folder 3)
      - Teacher’s Idea of an Ideal Parent, 1988-1990 (Box 349, Folder 4)
      - Teaching, 1986-1989 (Box 349, Folder 5)
      - Teaching Foreign Languages to Young Children, 1987-1989 (Box 349, Folder 6)
      - Tennessee Meiji Gakuin, 1986-1989 (Box 349, Folder 7)
      - Texas File – circa, 1990 (Box 349, Folder 8)
      - What’s a New Car Factory Telling Us About Education?, 1987-1989 (Box 349, Folder 9)
      - When Does Education Start?, 1988-1989 (Box 349, Folder 10)
      - Writing Skills, 1985-1989 (Box 349, Folder 11)
      - Year-Round School, 1989 (Box 349, Folder 12)
  - Sub-series B: Correspondence
    - UT President’s Papers – Correspondence, 1989-1990
      - General, 1989 (1 of 2) (Box 349, Folder 13)
      - General, 1989 (2 of 2) (Box 349, Folder 14)
      - General, 1990 (Box 349, Folder 15)
    - UT President’s Papers – Correspondence, 1990-1991 January
      - General, 1990 December (1 of 2) (Box 350, Folder 1)
      - General, 1990 December (2 of 2) (Box 350, Folder 2)
      - General, 1991 January (1 of 11) (Box 350, Folder 3)
      - General, 1991 January (2 of 11) (Box 350, Folder 4)
      - General, 1991 January (3 of 11) (Box 350, Folder 5)
      - General, 1991 January (4 of 11) (Box 350, Folder 6)
      - General, 1991 January (5 of 11) (Box 350, Folder 7)
      - General, 1991 January (6 of 11) (Box 350, Folder 8)
      - General, 1991 January (7 of 11) (Box 350, Folder 9)
      - General, 1991 January (8 of 11) (Box 350, Folder 10)
      - General, 1991 January (9 of 11) (Box 350, Folder 11)
    - UT President’s Papers – Correspondence, 1991 January-February
      - General, 1991 January (10 of 11) (Box 351, Folder 1)
      - General, 1991 January (11 of 11) (Box 351, Folder 2)
      - General, 1991 February (Box 351, Folder 3)
  - Sub-series C: Articles and Publications
    - UT President’s Papers – Articles and Publications, 1986-1991
      - “Report and Recommendations to the President of the United States”, 1986 December (1 of 2) (Box 352, Folder 1)
      - “Report and Recommendations to the President of the United States”, 1986 December (2 of 2) (Box 352, Folder 2)
      - “Democracy’s Next Generation”, 1989 (Box 352, Folder 3)
      - “College Admissions Tests: Opportunities or Roadblocks?”, 1988 June (Box 352, Folder 4)
      - The Wall Street Journal – Special Education Section, 1990 February 9 (Box 352, Folder 5)
      - “An Analysis of Equity in Tennessee School Finance”, 1988 June 30 (Box 352, Folder 6)
      - “An Analysis of Equity in Tennessee School Finance”, 1988 November 9-11 (Box 352, Folder 7)
      - “Sales Tax: Its effects on educational opportunity in Tennessee”, 1989 Winter (Box 352, Folder 8)
      - “Greater Knoxville Chamber of Commerce – B.E.S.T. Program”, 1989 (Box 352, Folder 9)
      - Department of Education Materials, 1990 (Box 352, Folder 10)
      - National board for Professional Teaching Standards Publications, 1988 (Box 352, Folder 11)
      - “Time for Results”, 1988-1991 (Box 352, Folder 12)
    - UT President’s Papers – Articles and Publications, 1988-1990; undated
      - “Ten Steps to Being America’s Education President”, 1988 October 12 (Box 353, Folder 1)
      - American Magazine, 1989-1990 (Box 353, Folder 2)
      - Forbes – Education Issues, 1988-1990 March (Box 353, Folder 3)
      - “Classroom Creativity You Can Bank On”, 1990 August (Box 353, Folder 4)
      - Harvard Magazine – “Is Higher Education Really Failing?”, 1990 May-June (Box 353, Folder 5)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1988-1990 (1 of 3) (Box 353, Folder 6)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1988-1990 (2 of 3) (Box 353, Folder 7)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1988-1990 (3 of 3) (Box 353, Folder 8)
      - Official Photographs, undated (Box 353, Folder 9)
    - UT President’s Papers – Articles and Publications, 1987-1992
      - “Network News & Views”, 1990 October (Box 354, Folder 1)
      - “Network News & Views”, 1990 November (Box 354, Folder 2)
      - “Knoxville of Yesteryear – A 1991 Photographic Calendar” (Box 354, Folder 3)
      - “National Geographic Society – The Wonders of Nature”, 1991 (Box 354, Folder 4)
      - Los Angeles Times Magazine, 1992 January 5 (Box 354, Folder 5)
      - “Americans and the Outdoors”, 1987 January 1 (1 of 2) (Box 354, Folder 6)
      - “Americans and the Outdoors”, 1987 January 1 (2 of 2) (Box 354, Folder 7)
- Series IX: Secretary of Education
  - Sub-series A: Administrative Materials
    - Secretary of Education – Administrative Materials, 1988-1992
      - Senate Confirmation – Confirmation Hearing Before the Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources Transcript, 1991 February 6 (Box 355, Folder 1)
      - Senate Confirmation – Letters to the Hill, 1991 February 15 (Box 355, Folder 2)
      - Senate Confirmation – Written Q’s and A’s, 1991 May (1 of 2) (Box 355, Folder 3)
      - Senate Confirmation – Written Q’s and A’s, 1991 May (2 of 2) (Box 355, Folder 4)
      - Senate Confirmation – Disqualifications After Confirmation, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 5)
      - Appointments to Committees, 1991 March 18 – 1993 January 20 (Box 355, Folder 6)
      - Memos to the President, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 7)
      - RNC Member Lists, 1988; 1992 (Box 355, Folder 8)
      - President’s Education Events, 1989 January 10 – 1992 March 27 (Box 355, Folder 9)
      - Cabinet Activities, 1991-1992 (Box 355, Folder 10)
      - Resumes, 1991 (Box 355, Folder 11)
      - Senior Advisor’s Retreat, 1991 August 28 (Box 355, Folder 12)
      - Hearings Before the Senate on Appropriations for the Department of Education, 1992 (Box 355, Folder 13)
    - Secretary of Education – Administrative Materials, 1991-1992
      - Fiscal Year 1992 Budget Request, 1991 (Box 356, Folder 1)